Hello everyone, in the 2024.2 version, the copy can maintain the conflict effect during simulation.
Right-click to copy and select the added simulation related functions in the menu.
Added three functions, freeze, activate and anti-activate.
Please note that when the hook is activated, the copy will participate in the simulation and conflict with the board, and will be heavily affected.
When the model is simulated, you can adjust its position by pressing the mouse button and holding down the copy button.
After activating the simulation for the two hooks, you can see that the weight of the hook affects the material of the package.
When dragging the copy, you can see that the material of the package will also move along with it.
Compositions such as the hook or the loop type are usually used in the simulation.
Compositions such as the hook or loop type are usually used in the simulation.
In this case, please reduce the conflict beast to get a more stable simulation effect.
The scale of the scale can be changed as you go through the simulation.
When the simulation is activated, you can adjust the weight of the object.
Go to the object window and find the object type, then go to the attribute editor to modify it.
Thank you.